this video is sponsored by audible how
cool is that I had a really random
shower thought this morning what if
somewhere in the world there's a person
called grain and everyone keeps
autocorrecting their name to grean and
what if they said who is this grean
character it's unlikely but you may also
notice that there is a small baby Yoda
in my hands now that's because last
episode at the end of last episode if
you didn't make it to the end of my last
episode shame on you but check it out I
got baby Yoda right here and last
episode I asked you to tell scar where
he was but I left this instead in fact
baby Yoda was removed from the scene
almost instantly after I was finished
recording so I left him baby why not
here if you want your baby boy back you
will have to play a little game with me
I will be in touch so
basically what I'm saying is scar is
going to have to work to get this baby
boy back it's a contingency plan we'll
see what happens but today is the day
where we play all of the mini games so
everyone is congregating and we are all
getting together so to give you a bit of
an update on the scoreboard it is
currently 2 to two and there are a few
games left so it is equally tied Tango's
game we won and impulses wacka stand we
also won so now we need to bring it all
to a head and we need to start playing
all the other games I'm only
participating in some so it's a real
team effort to see who wins so I don't
know what the first game is but here we
are we're about to start the first game
the first mini game that we're going to
play is dodge ball this one right here
now it's worth mentioning that all of
these mini games take like over half an
hour to play each some of them up to an
hour so I've had to cut as much as
possible to make this viewable for
everyone because a lot of the time we're
getting pretty competitive it's getting
pretty messy and it lasts a long time I
think there was over 4 hours of footage
so bear that in mind and you might want
to check out the other people's
perspectives if you want a full and more
detailed account of what happened in the
turf war finale okay then the game is
dodge ball the dodge ball is a splash
damage potion which you can grab from
those barrels at the back there all yall
are going to be splitting into two
different teams and you can only use one
potion at a time so between yourselves
you can discuss a little bit of strategy
who's going to throw the dodge ball and
once it's been thrown to the other side
it is then that team's turn to play good
luck everyone who's got it who's got it
oh oh they're doing a little
distraction oh she got a dou oh she got
dark oh
nice someone get aall someone get a ball
someone get my head I went to oh you
did you got to wake up you got to wake
up already okay nice nice y C's got it
should be it for you
guys
y two two all right all right mumbo's
loading up he takes the right at e wow
that was like a direct hit got ital has
got it got
it look how many heads in
there which one of us has it we want to
all run up we should make a wall and
then doc just like bust through the
wall
hey double hit oh no trip I caught it
can I have a go I I died straight away
go for it g yeah that was a b yeah yeah
good jot green I feel it Hees he wants
he wants his b you he's eying you big
time be an end be an
end all right he's looking
at he's
critical oh I miss yeah I think they're
just they're
Ling yes
okay come on
good
shot quick one maybe I think he might go
for you e no he's
not all right e it all comes down to
this one yes nailed
him I'm talking
about good
job oh run run run run
run oh nice double hit dou kill right on
the NOG in
it it took one for the te got him too I
got I got one I got a potion I got a
potion every time pretend to grab one
too yeah
okay out I'm just I'm
just oh yeah he got me he got me that's
all right that's all right quick shot
incoming come on just SC all right all
right stay split two on the left two on
the right that mansion's looking pretty
s take oh yeah yeah we have to alternate
anyway guys yeah yeah oh yeah sorry
didn't oh no okay okay okay took me out
watch where he's
going slam
dunk yes okay we won that game ultimate
success slam dunk kind of let the team
down in that last round but we did it so
now it is
32 on to the next game we could win this
while we set up the next mini game I'm
going to take this opportunity to
surprise you all with my real life face
and talk about today's sponsor
audible I'm not sure if this is a
sponsorship or more of a weird and
personal confession of mine audible is
the leading provider of audio
entertainment so podcasts audio books
that kind of thing and I absolutely love
it I listen wherever I can and whenever
there is a silent moment I just don't
use it like a normal human being I
listen when I'm cooking when I'm going
to sleep and of course when I'm grinding
away on Minecraft so what's weird about
that well I only listen to seven audio
books so why is my listening Time 1
month 15 days and 13 hours confession
time it's because I've listened to those
same seven audio books on repeat for the
last 4 years whenever I get to the end I
start all over again I know almost all
the words off by heart you tell and that
doesn't stop me listening but I wouldn't
be able to do it without audible on my
mobile phone and do I regret this
strange addiction of mine not at
all thank you to Audible for sponsoring
this video I'd like to make a couple of
audio book recommendations the first one
is The Hitchhikers Guide to the Galaxy
read by Steven fry or even any book read
by Steven fry and the second is only if
you're over 18 is a more Adult Book the
first 15 lies of Harry August by CLA
North it's about a guy who when he dies
is born back where he started but he
retains the memory of his previous Liv
it's a fantastic audio book so if you
want to join me for my non-stop listener
Thon then head on over to audible.com
for/ green or text Gan to 500500 and
sign up for a 30-day free trial on
Audible and if those don't take your
fancy then they have like a million
other titles on the platform it's insane
but you know I only need seven audio
books to get by check the link in the
description all b.com green now let's
get back into the episode so we won
dodgeball the next game that we're going
to play is this one floatage by Ren so
let's get into it welcome to
floatage whoa
wooho that was that was a c woo floated
is a very fun game we're going to be
blasting five of you into the sky while
the other team tries to shoot you down
you got to land on the platforms to get
a point and we're going to be playing
three rounds each and most points wins
at the end very simple floatage
contestants is everybody in the tube we
are good luck you round one
e boom
[Music]
grass lift
off get him get him
get get
him guys guys they did they get any oh
miss zero points they all missed
resistance now into the tube 0 0 after
round one
yeah a little
close all up in my grill there we go
nous oh get
ready here we
go come on come on come on come on come
on can I make it can I make it I'm not
going to make it I'm not going to make
it I'm not going to make
it did we get a point nice round three
guys the score is currently 1 Z on the
resistance side everybody's in the tube
ready to go who's up here with me okay
impul I'm coming I'm coming yeah is up
there do rock off hand impas right oh
okay okay are we ready all right got my
T ready y
ready can we shoot him goodbye friends
oh this is terrifying goodbye friends
I didn't who's the flat cannons I I
didn't okay fantastic performance by hip
three
points round yeah you got four onst
punch me in the face thank
you we are
ready are you ready all right who's our
shoters Shooters are you
ready XP crafted load it up load it up
yeah I'm loaded oh man oh good luck
everybody get get them right away guys
get them right away when they shoot
right out of the
tube here they come here they come cup
back take lock in get him no fell off
theform oh just
oh final round
[Music]
resist there we
go here we go oh no goodbye friend me
one aim for the tube time of the tube I
don't have it I don't have it don't
shoot me don't shoot me don't shoot me
this what all the pilot Wings training
was
for no I missed
[Music]
it four no way
won
[Music]
Sal so we have successfully won floatage
I think it's also worth mentioning after
that one in particular that these mini
games are going wrong like these games
were not play tested like none of them
would be absolutely perfect and we all
knew that and we all accept that for
example I blew up in floatage and missed
around scar got stuck in the tube a
couple of times these things happen
we're all cool with it and we all accept
what happens now the next game we're
going to play is Rip Zone this very
exciting Trident mini game by Etho
welcome Hermits to the rip
[Music]
zone so this is a PVP Trident Rip Tide
game your goal is to get as many points
as possible within about eight minutes
or so um your points you get one point
for handing in fish and you get five
points for handing in a player head from
the opponent's team in your gate down
there each team has their own gate that
opens up for about 15 seconds after you
unlock the three key spaces there by
throwing in a Cod and randomly we're
going to have fish spawning in the arena
and three contention zones you'll have
to fight over them and you have to
decide do you collect fish or do you
kill players we got four boys so I'm
thinking we need one fish boy two
delivery boys and one head hunter I
think I know which one I want to be the
fish boy head hunter you're fish boy
what I'm fish boy yeah we
go I'm in I'm in I rip tied there we
go oh man okay harder to hit than I
thought okay I got one fish I'm going to
go for one gate oh sorry dock my bad my
B why did you kill me oh
jeez okay the damage is real ah
I hit him twice and it didn't kill
him um oh no okay this is difficult I
need to get need get a kill I've got two
fish guys three fish I'm getting lots of
kills here Ren Ren Dro me one fish lot
kills I got loads of kills here I got it
I got I got heads I got heads I got two
heads I need one more fish to open the
gate guys guys guys go please open it up
yeah Ren
please the the top gate needs to be
triggered top one yep that one I got Cub
I got three heads please open the door
there we go another one oh okay i' to 15
points I got 15 points yep I found a
trident on the
ground get him all right I got load I
loads ah head I'm try to I'm trying to
open the other one here all right I'm
running okay left one is done green
where's the one you triggered that was
the one it's over on the left hand side
who's going for it Ren's going for
it all right here quick
nice nice nice that was big points that
was big points need more heads okay all
right got him got him I got load of
heads again we need to open up wait I
got a Cod head does that count I'm
opening the gate I'm opening
the I got a lot of trident if anybody
needs guys Bal is the farmer someone
take out Bal do lots of farming on that
side on the side fish thing I mean oh
dude man oh no
there should be plenty of heads in front
of it if they didn't pick him up oh I oh
I died from full damage I'm here I'm
here farming I'm farming him go for it
I've got a lot of kills freaking God go
in there it's a difficult to toss in
okay here we go it's better to stand in
the water to toss I just saw okay I got
cup with a lot of right someone open the
door uh I think it's been reset okay we
need to open the door quick it's game
over game over
over all right everybody ready to hear
the scores yeah ready I'm I'm going to
put each of your boxes on your side you
can take a peek and then peek at the
other guy's
box going to do us like
[Music]
that it's pretty clear just from looking
at it but Crimson the m resistance got
107 and the hip the warp side got
34 yikes why is my head the only one in
your box guys what this is we got do
well come on me and gots nice man so the
reason Play Everybody the reason for
this is cuz we were submitting our own
heads to save it from Hep taking the
points for them yeah you did the good
man that well that was amazing
yeah great game we won rip Zone by a
absolute mile whoa is that oh
what did you
see Vanishing
hun what half the water's
Vanishing okay enough of that the next
game that we are playing is this one a
maze by doc Ren is going to have to try
and get me navigate through this maze
let's go all right guys welcome to the
um yeah a maze
amazing amazing maze very quick
explanation it's a maze you run around
in the Maze there are block spawning the
best block in the game melium as we know
you got to return it to the middle you
can see your return stations marked out
with mycelium in Grass the game runs for
about 8 minutes we have the spotters up
here they are allowed to tell where to
run and where to go to help and um yeah
that's pretty much it if you are ready
um pull your levers on your Redstone
lamps and the game will actually start
right away so if you want to split up in
groups to your left is going to be your
first Target block but oh yeah I guess
yeah I got it okay no uh okay around the
corner there now yep oh there's two
blocks here oh wow they are dispensing
very fast they are dispensing very
quickly I'm going to put this in which
side do I go that there go I've
submitted six points yep around there
around the corner oh my goodness okay I
think I have enough I have enough I need
need to submit it to the middle okay go
let's get you to the middle then go
through the the
closest run it's a dead end there's
loads of oh my
goodness no Jes okay that's Madness
that's Madness so your left and my left
are not the same thing I'm no I'm trying
to do your right I'm trying to do your
right turn right got mycelium I got 16
mycelium oh okay the hogins are tracking
you they're tracking you they're
currently trapped in the room if you
take that right run run
run there's a hog in there this dead end
is it yes it's dead end you're
trapped there we go that one yep oh my
goodness okay the other doors open but
there's hoglands right on the other side
of this wall I
don't oh nicely done nicely done get out
of there open real soon I see oh the
door's just
opened okay there's one behind you one
behind you try get get away a dead end
yep oh I fell I fell mistakes have been
made same route again loads of my half
okay half time half time woo brain right
left left left are we still playing or
not
hoglins I don't know I'm not actually
sure oh no oh no we were still playing
dude oh we were it was just the halfway
point oh dang it okay this is a we don't
get a 15minute break
okay what are we doing hogging in the
middle
careful's my left and right turn right
turn right perfect turn
left turn right turn right turn
left turn left why does my spotter not
know left and
right yep go back to the middle there's
lots of stackage there hogging right on
you double hogl action double hling
action oh no okay there's one waiting
for you oh Jee they hit like a truck H
you are not giving me the correct left
and right right oh my
gosh someone help me there's another
blue door that's right the center you're
at the center you're at the center dude
it's so close there's more oh the dude I
there's hogl over there you got to trust
the ren voice in your head man game over
game over it's over time's up time's
up okay there is Three Stacks and nine
three stacks and nine on my
celium and two stacks
and land
slide that was yeah yeah GG's
G get his building hands ready and our
final mini game is this one The
Showdown by Scar so let's get into it
heredes welcome to Showdown this is a
bit of Tower Defense capture the flag
and a bit of paintball mixed in and as
you can see you are on your appropriate
teams the melium team excuse me that's
something gross and the beautiful
luscious greatest team of all time the
grass team over here that's so the goal
is to get the other source block the
other source block is kept in their
vaults same on each side you have to
have two players to push the button open
the vault take your Source block and
bring it up to the top of your preferred
mushroom or three place it on the
pedestal winning condition you win the
game let's go okay you're going defense
impulse yep going defense Etho let's
just don't stop to shoot shoot shoot and
just keep running okay shoot on the run
here we go go go go go go try to jump
over a few honey blocks there oh it
worked you got out fast I
did go just ignore them uh I'm going to
go
right I'm going I'm behind the lines oh
right in Tango's face oh they got eyes
on us that didn't back oh man it is hard
to make Headway huh
uh-huh me oh yeah yep I'm here okay okay
go go go go go I'm by the button need
second push coming up coming up coming
up coming
up oh I can't I can't Ready Set I'm
hiding by the button go go go go go oh I
couldn't get it oh I
just so much I tried to I I tried to
press the button and blew myself up yeah
that might have been what I did to okay
I think they're pushing now they're push
yeah they're pushing hard they're
pushing hard they're on the button false
on the button
come on come on the other button quick
quick nice nice nice let's try push here
run run run run side side side need to
get them we're not going to get we're
not going to get in without them y yep
yep trying to help trying to help nice
okay I'm here oh should be in I'm going
to go for it see if I can get around him
ready 3 two oh so close so close Okay
I'm going to go for the button ready
three two one press it press it press it
it's open it's open it's open I'm so low
I'm so I di in oh no so close almost got
I'm running it now it close oh no
no that was cl keep pushing keep
pushing okay perfect Cubs down walls are
up let's go I'm going right I'm at I'm
at the red button I'm at the button I'm
at the other one on the right 3 2 one go
one go go go go go it's open get in it's
open going in okay hey get the button
get get get the block got it got it got
it if you can go for a run uh run I'm
coming to help oh they know I'm in here
though right they're going to try to get
in though let me let me know when you
feel like I can I can be clear to run
out oh I don't know I don't think they
don't they don't see you right now keep
keep
crouching okay if we can kill them here
green yeah let me know when yeah we'll
let you know we'll let you know when
it's clear in fact I'm going to TNT that
side oh they did they figure it out yep
yep yep Tango's in here Tang's in here
no I'm trying to work in my way out oh
he got me I don't think I don't think
they know you're in I got the block I
got the block go go go go go go go got
my totem equipped when you're ready I'm
going to give you you we're defending
you I'm I'm full health here I'm down
okay coming through oh man I got you I
got you I'm going I'm going I'm going go
run you extra end Pearl oh they they're
behind you guys y they're behind you but
I got I got you I got I got you
oh I think I killed you no we got to
toss the grass block now right yeah yeah
yeah you got to TOS oh man oh man the
end Pearl trick is good though the end
PE trick is the one it gets you but how
do we get out we got to get back safely
is the problem take two ends okay it's
on we won what they won they won I guess
I they put it in they need to put it in
front of it oh no oh how did they get
that snap y they must snuck it in while
we were doing that we were so worried
about Etho coming back they got behind
you and grabbed it without us even
knowing wow
GG well it looks like the mycelium
thoroughly won the majority of the games
which means the turf war has been
officially declared over all there is
left to do now is to bring everyone
together and let them know the bad SL
good news depending on which team you're
on personally I'm just glad that this is
all over welcome Turf War participants
we have fought long and hard to create
these mini games and then we fought long
and hard to win the min games and we are
going to reveal who is the winner I
think we already know who the winner is
but we're going to do it anyways so the
viewers yeah the the
viewers so Hep finished with three whole
points they won Showdown scar mini game
grass jump and my game rings of death
and the melium resistance won so many
games that I had to make the scoreboard
bigger so Absolut
Landslide we won dodgeball Wacker stand
escape the mycelium rip Zone amaz and
flage meaning the mycelium resistance
take the win and Scar you've got to
build the back of my Mansion oh yeah
W who
GG
Tada well done resistance PG guys scar
gbody
G and I got the backside I still don't
even have my baby Yoda
pack farewell pumpkin pie hello chorus
fruit how's that chorus tasting so all
wagers are now final if you made a wager
then that you have to do whatever the
mycelium resistance told you to do or
however you did it I think vub is a
delivery boy
now I am yeah does this mean that
genuinely the shopping district is going
to stay as myum though cuz it is really
ugly no no no no no war part two if
that's the case War part
two no I was going to say the agreement
is that the losing side has to restore
the shopping district back to grass and
make it pretty still Better Block yeah
oh yeah it was never about the block
let's be honest in summary we we ruined
the shopping district and we made you
fix it so I think it's just been a
winwin win win win well done resistance
we we we did it we beat City
hallo for the principal oneir the
principal let's have a hurrah for the
winners here yeah 1
two hey he hey hey hey he just had to
sterilize you guys from all your
spores GG everyone that was awesome myum
is ugly
though well that is it the mycelium
resistance won by a genuine Landslide it
was very unexpected especially as we
were two points to zero at the start of
this so this is the reverse sweep coming
in here and my goodness was this amazing
like I didn't expect my silly mycelium
block placing outside the barge would
result in a fullscale war on the
hermitcraft server let alone a giant
miname Olympics which got dare I say it
very competitive in the end
we all had a fantastic time and everyone
is happy and I've got to say a huge
thank you to all the Hermits who
participated this story line has been
something really special but it is
definitely come to a close now but look
at the mini games look at the effort and
the time that people put in to make
these mini games happen on such a short
notice
absolutely amazing I hope you have
thoroughly thoroughly enjoyed this story
line but now it is time to go back
to
basics for now though I think that's all
I've got time for and I shall see you in
the next episode and also don't forget
to check out that audible description if
you sign up it really does help me out
and uh I really I really do genuinely
recommend audible a lot so check that
link in the description and uh sign up I
mean it's it's free 30 days free trial
see if you like it all
right bye